<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xwikidoc>
<web>FileCheck</web>
<name>ResourceImprovementEmail</name>
<language></language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>0</translation>
<parent></parent>
<creator>XWiki.LudovicDubost</creator>
<author>XWiki.jkl1231</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.jkl1231</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1194209324000</creationDate>
<date>1234297500000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1266877071000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.1</version>
<title></title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<comment>Importé depuis un le XAR</comment>
<minorEdit>false</minorEdit>
<syntaxId>xwiki/1.0</syntaxId>
<hidden>false</hidden>
<object>
<class>
<name>XWiki.TagClass</name>
<customClass></customClass>
<customMapping></customMapping>
<defaultViewSheet></defaultViewSheet>
<defaultEditSheet></defaultEditSheet>
<defaultWeb></defaultWeb>
<nameField></nameField>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<tags>
<cache>0</cache>
<disabled>0</disabled>
<displayType>select</displayType>
<multiSelect>1</multiSelect>
<name>tags</name>
<number>1</number>
<prettyName>Tags</prettyName>
<relationalStorage>1</relationalStorage>
<separator> </separator>
<separators> ,|</separators>
<size>30</size>
<unmodifiable>0</unmodifiable>
<values></values>
<classType>com.xpn.xwiki.objects.classes.StaticListClass</classType>
</tags>
</class>
<name>FileCheck.ResourceImprovementEmail</name>
<number>0</number>
<className>XWiki.TagClass</className>
<guid>458b83bb-4859-4dd8-909a-00d5794c74ed</guid>
<property>
<tags/>
</property>
</object>
<content>From: filecheck@curriki.org
To: $email
Subject: Curriki Resource Improvement Request - $assettitle

Dear Curriki Member $membername,

Thank you for creating a learning resource, $assettitle, in Curriki.

Our preliminary file check found that one of the following is true for this resource:

 - You created a resource from a template or started building a curriculum, but you haven't developed content in it.
 - You created a resource to test the system or begin a draft, but it is mostly incomplete.
 - Your resource is a broken link or file.
 - Your resources are without immediate educational value for the instructional context.

Due to this issue, your resource has been given a 'Private' setting under Access Privileges; other members of the Curriki community will not be able to view or access this resource.

The Curriki repository offers free learning resources to a global education and learning community; making search results useful and resources valuable is the responsibility of members.

It would be great if you could return and update your resource, offering something of real value for the global education community! Here's how to proceed:

1.    Go to the Curriki site (http://www.curriki.org) and log in.
2.    Use the left menu to go to "My Contributions" under the "My Curriki" heading.
3.    Find the resource you wish to update and click "Edit" for a single file or "Build Up" for a collection or folder from the options on the right. 
4.    If you click Edit, you will be taken to edit the resource in the Content tab, where you can add content and save your complete resource. If you click Build Up, you will see options for adding resources into your collection or folder.
5.    Once you have completed your revisions and your resource is ready for sharing with others who visit Curriki, click "Edit Info" for the resource in My Contributions and, when viewing the editable settings in the Information tab, choose "Public" or "Protected" under Access Privileges, then save the new setting.

If you would like more information regarding Curriki's content screening process, or if you would like to discuss this particular submission, please email filecheck@curriki.org.</content></xwikidoc>
