<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<xwikidoc>
<web>Main</web>
<name>McNealy</name>
<language></language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>0</translation>
<parent>Main.Board</parent>
<creator>XWiki.ABader</creator>
<author>XWiki.ABader</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.ABader</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1163569589000</creationDate>
<date>1163569649000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1163569649000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.2</version>
<title>McNealy</title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<content>1 Board of Directors

#titlebar("Scott G. McNealy" "" "" "purple")
&lt;br&gt;
__Member, Board of Directors__
&lt;br&gt;
As a member of Curriki’s Board of Directors and the visionary behind the idea for Curriki, Scott G. McNealy will help guide the organization’s goal of making world-class curricula universally accessible.  

Currently Chairman of Sun Microsystems, Inc.'s Board of Directors, McNealy co-founded the company in 1982. He served as chief executive officer and chairman at Sun for 22 years, steering the Company to constant innovation in open, network computing. He also helped transform the company from a Silicon Valley start-up to a leading provider of network computing infrastructure with more than 30,000 employees worldwide, all while positioning the Company as the model of corporate integrity.

McNealy is known for his longstanding commitment to education and advocacy for open and competitive business practices. In March 2004, he led Sun to create the Global Education &amp; Learning Community (GELC) to leverage open source to provide affordable lifelong learning for all students, no matter where they are. GELC was spun off in 2006 as an independent 501(c)(3) nonprofit now known as Curriki – the Global Education &amp; Learning Community.  

McNealy holds a Bachelors of Arts from Harvard with a Bachelors of Arts in Economics and received a Masters of Business Administration from Stanford University. 


</content></xwikidoc>