<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xwikidoc>
<web>Main</web>
<name>Volunteer</name>
<language></language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>0</translation>
<parent>Main.WebHome</parent>
<creator>XWiki.martagirdea</creator>
<author>XWiki.dward</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.dward</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1174224849000</creationDate>
<date>1181316772000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1181316772000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.16</version>
<title></title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<comment>Changed parent to Main.WebHome</comment>
<object>
<class>
<name>XWiki.TagClass</name>
<customClass></customClass>
<customMapping></customMapping>
<defaultViewSheet></defaultViewSheet>
<defaultEditSheet></defaultEditSheet>
<defaultWeb></defaultWeb>
<nameField></nameField>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<tags>
<cache>0</cache>
<displayType>select</displayType>
<multiSelect>1</multiSelect>
<name>tags</name>
<number>1</number>
<prettyName>Tags</prettyName>
<relationalStorage>1</relationalStorage>
<separator> </separator>
<separators> ,|</separators>
<size>30</size>
<unmodifiable>0</unmodifiable>
<values></values>
<classType>com.xpn.xwiki.objects.classes.StaticListClass</classType>
</tags>
</class>
<name>Main.Volunteer</name>
<number>0</number>
<className>XWiki.TagClass</className>
<property>
<tags/>
</property>
</object>
<content>#titlebar("Volunteer with Curriki" "" "" "purple" )

Welcome to Curriki Volunteers, your home for learning about volunteer opportunities and connecting with other Curriki volunteers.  Whether you're connected through a business, academic, or community organization, or an individual looking to pitch in, we're glad you're here! 


#subtitlebar("Individual volunteers" "" "" "purple" )

If you are new to Curriki, take a look at the [FAQ page&gt;Main.FAQ] to learn more about Curriki and why volunteers like you are essential to our work.

Once you are familiar with Curriki, please [become a member&gt;Main.JoinCurriki].  Registering as a member enables you to use all of our tools and connect with other volunteers and projects.

#subtitlebar("Group volunteers" "" "" "purple" )

Business, academic, and community organizations can create a special partnership with Curriki to develop materials or support their members.  For more information on how your organization can partner with Curriki, send an email to {mailto:volunteer@curriki.org}.

Sun Microsystems, Curriki's founding company, encourages employees to volunteers and/or donate to Curriki to help educators worldwide.  

The National Association of Retired Teachers is a Curriki partner. NRTA members can contribute and review Curriki materials via special partner projects.

#subtitlebar("Keep up to date" "" "" "purple" )

Curriki volunteers will post project information, pod casts and blogs on the Curriki repository.  Links to these will be available on this page.

#subtitlebar("Get Started" "" "" "purple" )

*Contribute*: As a registered user of Curriki, use MyCurriki to add your own material:  books, lesson plans, tests, blog, etc.  Make your materials available to the Curriki community.  Add other Curriki materials to your collection and experiment with the editing tools.
  
*Collaborate*:  Invite colleagues and friends to join Curriki and work with you on improving materials in the repository or adding new content.

*Review*:  Browse the Curriki repository for subject matter that interests you, read the material, and provide comments via the Curriki reviewer template (coming soon).

*Translate*:  Apply your language skills to translate the pages into another language.  Post your translated pages in the repository and send an email to  {mailto:translations@curriki.org} with the information about your work.

*Test*:  New Curriki software releases need beta testers.  Email {mailto:beta@curriki.org} for information on the latest release, new features, and how to provide feedback.

#titlebar("Join Curriki now!" "Register" "Main.JoinCurriki" "blue" )
</content></xwikidoc>