<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xwikidoc>
<web>XWiki</web>
<name>ToTranslate</name>
<language>hi</language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>1</translation>
<parent></parent>
<creator>XWiki.ShermanTank</creator>
<author>XWiki.ShermanTank</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.ShermanTank</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1208538192000</creationDate>
<date>1208538719000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1215461923000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.1</version>
<title></title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<comment>Importé depuis un le XAR</comment>
<minorEdit>false</minorEdit>
<syntaxId>xwiki/1.0</syntaxId>
<hidden>false</hidden>
<object>
<class>
<name>XWiki.TagClass</name>
<customClass></customClass>
<customMapping></customMapping>
<defaultViewSheet></defaultViewSheet>
<defaultEditSheet></defaultEditSheet>
<defaultWeb></defaultWeb>
<nameField></nameField>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<tags>
<cache>0</cache>
<disabled>0</disabled>
<displayType>select</displayType>
<multiSelect>1</multiSelect>
<name>tags</name>
<number>1</number>
<prettyName>Tags</prettyName>
<relationalStorage>1</relationalStorage>
<separator> </separator>
<separators> ,|</separators>
<size>30</size>
<unmodifiable>0</unmodifiable>
<values></values>
<classType>com.xpn.xwiki.objects.classes.StaticListClass</classType>
</tags>
</class>
<name>XWiki.ToTranslate</name>
<number>0</number>
<className>XWiki.TagClass</className>
<guid>378808c9-b62b-4cc8-b910-8e0b06ff4ea5</guid>
<property>
<tags/>
</property>
</object>
<content># header texts

loginUsername=username
loginPassword=password
loginRememberme=Remember Me
loginForgot=Forgot Login
headerLoginGo=Go &amp;#xBB;

BecomeMember_part1=Become
BecomeMember_part2=a Member

headerWelcome=Welcome {0}
headerMyCurriki=My Curriki


##IGNORE EVERYTHING BELOW

# header texts

headerFindResource=Find a Learning Resource or Search the Site
headerBrowse=Browse
AdvancedSearch=Advanced Search
headerSearchGo=Go &amp;#xBB;

# general

docs.privacyPolicy=Privacy Policy
dateFormat=MM/dd/yy
dateFormatLong=MMMM d, yyyy
publishedby=Published by {0}
navigationHome=Home
createdby=Created by


#Main.About

docs.partnersAndSponsors=Partners and Sponsors
docs.contactUs=Contact Us
docs.TOS=Terms of Use
docs.boards=Board of Directors and Advisors
docs.leadership=Leadership Team
docs.currikiFAQ=Curriki FAQs

docs.sponsors=Sponsors

about.currikiIsACommunity=Curriki is more than your average Website; we're a community of educators, learners and committed education experts who are working together to create quality materials that will benefit teachers and students around the world.
about.currikiIsAnOnlineEnvironment=Curriki is an online environment created to support the development and free distribution of world-class educational materials to anyone who needs them. Our name is a play on the combination of 'curriculum' and 'wiki' which is the technology we're using to make education universally accessible.

docs.learnMore=Learn More
about.aboutCurriki=about Curriki

about.whoWeAre.subtitle=Who Are We?
about.whoWeAre=Curriki is the result of work done for GELC - the Global Education and Learning Community - an online project started by Sun Microsystems to develop works for education in a collaborative effort. The leadership team consists of people with a long-time commitment to exploring the use of technology to improve education. 

about.meetThe=Meet the

about.partners.subtitle=Curriki is a Community
caption.seeOurPartners=See Our Partners
about.partners.whoTheyAre=In addition to members like you, we have support and funding from a variety of partners. These are individuals and organizations that are convinced that making world-class materials freely available to educators around the world is a key part of improving children's learning.
about.partners.whatTheyDo=These early members and supporters are educators and organizations that believe in Curriki's approach of using technology to provide freely available learning resources.  They have generously allowed us to utilize existing materials and have created resources especially for Curriki, as well. 

about.seeWhatsHere.subtitle=See What's Here
about.seeWhatsHere=You can see the resources and courses that are already here by clicking the Search button at the top of the screen.   Want to be a part of our community?



#Main.BlogRss

blogRss.title=RSS Feed of the Wiki Blog
blogRss.description=RSS Feed of the Wiki Blog



#Main.Board

board.advisors.title=Curriki Advisors

board.advisors.info=Curriki provides an avenue for educators and education decision makers from all over the world to come together as a global education and learning community. We aim to create and promote an open infrastructure for developing and distributing curricula based on a common set of open standards.

board.directorsAndAvisors.subtitle=Curriki Board of Directors and Advisors
board.directorsAndAvisors.info=We have a diverse board of advisors representing many different countries, concerns and points of view. These advisors share our dedication to helping Curriki create and promote an open infrastructure for freely available learning resources.

board.directorsAndAvisors.directors=Board of Directors
board.directorsAndAvisors.honoraryCommittee=Honorary Committee

board.directorsAndAvisors.currikiAdvisoryBoardMembers=Curriki Advisory Board Members



#Main.BrowseSearch

browseSearch.rebuilding=Started index rebuild with {0} documents. Will take some time depending on the number of pages/attachments.

browseSearch.bySubject=Browse by Subject
browseSearch.info=Click a subject to see a list of all the learning resources in that category. The number in parentheses shows how many matching results are on the site
right now.

browseSearch.noResult=You search did not return matching resources



#Main.Contact

contact.title=Contact Us

contact.byMail=By Mail
contact.byPhoneOrFax=By Phone or Fax
contact.byEmail=By EMail

contact.contribute.subtitle=Contribute Content Collections
contact.contribute.info=If you're a publisher or other organization with a substantial collection of K-12 curriculum, share it with the global education community. Email us and tell us about your content:
contact.press.subtitle=For Press Inquiries, please contact:

#Main.Donate

donate.title=Donate

donate.donateToCurriki=Donate to Curriki
donate.donateToCurriki.infos=Curriki is a nonprofit community that relies on the support of companies, foundations, and individuals to realize our vision of a truly global education and learning community.  Your donation makes it possible for educators worldwide to develop, share, and access the highest quality curricula and learning resources with teachers and learners around the globe.

donate.donationMatching=Donation Matching
donate.donationMatching.infos1=For a limited time, __all donations will be matched, dollar-for-dollar, in a corresponding donation made in Sun's name by a very generous benefactor__.   Thus if you donate $1,000 it will be matched by the benefactor and will actually be a donation of $2,000 to Curriki. Additionally, donations from Sun employees can further be matched by Sun's existing matching gift program.  For Sun employees, this could make your $1,000 donation worth $3,000*.
donate.donationMatching.infos2=If you are not a Sun employee, please check with your current employer as they may have similar matching gift programs.
donate.donationMatching.byMail=__To make a donation by mail, please make your check or money order payable to "Curriki" and send to:__
donate.donationMatching.online=__To make a donation electronically:__
donate.donationMatching.online.infos1=Select a donation amount or choose "Other" to enter a different amount.  Then click the __Donate__ button to go to PayPal's secure transaction page.
donate.donationMatching.paypal.infos=All donation amounts are in USD and your financial information is kept private.  Select an amount and click the PayPal button to make your contribution.
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD10=$10.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD25=$25.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD50=$50.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD100=$100.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD250=$250.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.USD500=$500.00
donate.donationMatching.paypal.other=Other - Enter Your Donation Amount on the Next Page
donate.donationMatching.paypal.isSunEmployee=Are you a Sun Microsystems employee?

donate.donationMatching.sunMatching=*For the general donor, the benefactor will give $1 for each $1 donation. For Sun employees, under the company's existing matching gift program, Sun will also match employee donations.   When combined with the benefactor's match for Curriki, a $1 donation from a Sun employee could mean a total of $3 for Curriki.    Sun employees that would like information and FAQ's on Sun's process for matching donations should email us at:

donate.donationMatching.deductibleTaxes=Curriki is a 501(c)(3) not-for-profit organization; contributions are tax deductible.



#Main.EventCalendar

eventCalendar.title=Event Calendar
eventCalendar.previous=Previous Month
eventCalendar.next=Next Month

eventCalendar.eventList=Event List
eventCalendar.eventList.useEditObject=Use [edit object&gt;{0}] to modify or remove existing events.
eventCalendar.newEvent=New Event
eventCalendar.newEvent.location=Location:
eventCalendar.newEvent.startDate=Start date inclusive (dd/mm/yyyy):
eventCalendar.newEvent.endDate=End date inclusive (dd/mm/yyyy):
eventCalendar.newEvent.decription=Description:
eventCalendar.newEvent.button=Add this event



#Main.FAQ 

faq.title=FAQs

faq.info=Here are answers to some frequently asked questions about Curriki

faq.q01=What is Curriki?
faq.q01.r1=Curriki, a play on the words ?curriculum? and ?wiki?, is a nonprofit organization that is building the first and only Internet site for Open Source Curriculum (OSC), which will provide universal access to free curricula and instructional materials for grades K-12.
faq.q01.r2=We are focusing initially on developing an online repository for K-12 curricula in the areas of mathematics, science, technology, reading and language arts, and languages. We want this repository to attract everyone ? from educators, students and parents, to programmers, instructional designers, authors and public officials ? throughout the world to contribute or freely access quality learning materials. 

faq.q02=Why was Curriki started
faq.q02.r1=Curriki was conceived from the idea that technology can play a crucial role in breaking down the barriers of the Education Divide ? the division of inequality that prevents children worldwide from access to quality education.
faq.q02.r2=Today, educators are searching for ways to deliver first-class, cost-effective learning resources and opportunities to their students.  Learners are becoming discouraged by the mounting costs for textbooks, and the availability of other credible resources.
faq.q02.r3=Curriki will make learning possible for anyone, anywhere in the world. This will drive personal growth and give opportunity to those who wouldn?t otherwise have it. Perhaps, this exposure to education will even reveal the children who could solve some of our biggest problems of tomorrow.

faq.q03=Can you explain Open Source Curriculum (OSC)?
faq.q03.r1=The best place to start is by defining the concept of open source technology. Open source refers to a method that opens up access to source materials or codes.  It is created by a development community rather than a single vendor and typically programmed by volunteers from many groups.  The code of open source software is free and available to anyone who would like to use it or modify it for his or her own purposes.
faq.q03.r2=By using the open source process for education, we are empowering educational professionals to become an active community in the creation of world-class curricula.

faq.q04=How is Curriki different from other e-learning sites?
faq.q04.r1=Curriki is different in two ways: (1) we focus on a complete curricula solution, not just a textbook or lesson plans, but a comprehensive course of instruction and assessment. Curriki.org will include easy-to-use tools for creating curriculum packets out of content assets available on the site. (2) We have a unique approach to curriculum development, distribution and evaluation that is represented by the organization?s 3-D model: curriculum developed through community contributors, delivered globally and whose impact is determined by project and by individual.

faq.q05=Is Curriki ready to use now?
faq.q05.r1=Yes, www.curriki.org is open and available.  Curriki is working with a variety of partners to contribute a diverse collection of curriculum to our repository. In early 2007, we?ll be adding more functionality and resources, including the ability to create courses, to contribute and access open source textbooks, as well as the capability to collaborate and communicate about curriculum online.

faq.q06=How can I contribute to or edit curricula available at www.curriki.org?
faq.q06.r1=There are a variety of ways to contribute curricula at www.curriki.org.  You can use our unique online tools to write a textbook or build a curriculum.
faq.q06.r2=Additionally, starting in January 2007, our unique Textbook Wiki enables groups of teachers or professors to take a curriculum framework and use the tools to create and edit a book map, or sections and pages of an instructional textbook.
faq.q06.r3=Our Currikulum Builder enables users to select individual lesson plans, course syllabi, learning activities, scope and sequence hierarchies, and other educational elements found at www.curriki.org to build a complete, fully-integrated curriculum.

faq.q07=Who evaluates materials on the Curriki site?
faq.q07.r1=Curriki is led by a seasoned team of experts in the education and technology arenas. Their experience as teachers, authors and technologists has given them the hands-on understanding of what it takes to make quality and easy-to-use curricula. Leveraging Curriki?s resources and leadership, led by its Chief Academic Officer, Curriki will expertly manage the curricula to ensure the community makes the best decisions.  It is this trust in the right leadership, tools and community that will enable the development and distribution of quality curricula.  

faq.q08=Can you tell me more about Curriki?s leadership team?
faq.q08.r1=Curriki?s leadership team includes:
faq.q08.r1.l1=Dr. Barbara ?Bobbi? Kurshan, Executive Director. Dr. Kurshan has spent her whole career committed to using technology to improve children?s learning. She has founded several successful companies focused on technology and education. She is the author of several dozen books and articles on teaching and technology, community building for educators and creating the global classroom.  
faq.q08.r1.l2=Anne Schreiber, Chief Academic Officer, has numerous years of experience as a multi-media publisher, product designer and educator. Focusing on curriculum development, she has held posts at Grow Networks/McGraw-Hill, Scholastic, bigchalk and Sesame Workshop. Anne began her career as an elementary school teacher and has authored more than a dozen books for young children.  
faq.q08.r1.l3=Joshua Marks, Chief Technology Officer, has over two decades of experience using emerging technologies to address market needs in education. He was instrumental in launching Harcourt Education?s e-learning group, has spearheaded innovative technology-based pilot programs to aid student learning, and developed numerous education-focused software programs.

faq.q09=How can I use Curriki materials?
faq.q09.r1=Anyone with access to the Internet can use the material found on Curriki to teach themselves or others. Whether its algebra, reading, or physics, they will be able to access the curricula online, print it, and/or save it to a CD.

faq.q10=Is Curriki the same organization as the Global Education &amp;amp; Learning Community (GELC)?
faq.q10.r1=Yes.  In March 2004, Sun Microsystems launched the Global Education &amp;amp; Learning Community (GELC).  In 2006, Sun spun GELC off as an independent 501(c)(3) nonprofit to focus on building a repository of curricula and to create an online community for this repository. The organization changed its name to Curriki in 2006 to capture the spirit of community-driven learning excellence and the delivery of Open Source Curricula.

faq.q11=Why should I get involved?
faq.q11.r1=Because helping others to learn and overcome the Education Divide is simply the right thing to do.  With your input, we can help foster the exchange of ideas, whether among students and parents, or curriculum developers and educators ? all in a global, interactive community that makes it fun and rewarding to make a difference.  
faq.q11.r2=Your assistance can come in many important forms. Actively participate in our community. Use the curricula. Provide us with feedback. Support the community financially. And most importantly, spread the word.

faq.q12=How can I contact Curriki?
faq.q12.r1=send an email to 



#Main.FeaturedContent

featuredContent.title=Featured Content
featuredContent.titlebar_right=Go to the featured content section
featuredContent.infos=Look at some of the exciting Learning Resources shared by our content partners. They're yours to download and use .  Keep checking back, there will be thousands of more resources for you to use as our community grows.
featuredContent.fhsst.subtitle=Free High School Science Texts
featuredContent.fhsst.infos=FHSST has posted segments of their open source science and mathematics textbooks for Grades 10 - 12 on Curriki. These books are the creations of a South Africa-based world-wide open source community.
featuredContent.wlc.subtitle=World Leadership Corps
featuredContent.wlc.infos=WLC is a service program dedicated to helping create the leaders of tomorrow. Volunteers are currently working in China, Sweden andthe Dominican Republic developing programs to raise awareness of global issues among local populations.
featuredContent.tapestry.subtitle=The Tapestry Project
featuredContent.tapestry.infos=The Tapestry Project, under the aegis of the UN Millennium Project, is encouraging young leaders to create digital stories to raise awareness of key issues in their countries.
featuredContent.nroc.subtitle=NROC
featuredContent.nroc.infos=NROC is an online community of educators, designers, technologists, and administrators working together to develop high-quality online education that is available to everyone.


featuredContent.contribute.clickLinks=Do you have content to contribute? Click the link to contribute.
featuredContent.contribute.publisherPartner=If you're a publisher or other organization with a substantial collection of K-12 curriculum, share it with the global education community. Email us and tell us about your content:
featuredContent.contribute.members=If you're not a member, you need to register to be able to contribute. [Click here to register&gt;Register].

#Main.featuredPartner

featuredPartner.title=Featured Partner
featuredPartner.titlebar_right=Go to the featured partner section


#Main.Leadership

leadership.title=Curriki Leadership Team

leadership.dedicatedTeam=A dedicated team of education and technology professionals has been working to create the Curriki community.
leadership.leadershipTeam=Leadership Team

leadership.bobbi.qualifiedName=Dr. Barbara -Bobbi- Kurshan, Executive Director

leadership.bobbi.part1=Dr. Kurshan has spent her career committed to using technology to improve children's learning. She has founded several successful companies focused on technology and education. In her new position as the Executive Director of Curriki, she plans to build a global community that will provide the best open source curricula just a click away.
leadership.bobbi.part2=Earlier in her career, Dr. Kurshan developed the first children's software products for Microsoft - Creative Writer and Fine Artist and also created award-winning products for McGraw-Hill, Apple, CCC (Pearson) and others.  As a professor, she helped students research the impact of technology on learning.  Dr. Kurshan also publishes articles based on personal research exploring women's attitudes toward technology, how kids use computers, and new ways of learning through understanding.  She has been quoted in many influential journals and serves as a reviewer and advisor to research projects for the National Science Foundation and other government and business groups.
leadership.bobbi.part3=Currently, Dr. Kurshan serves on the boards of WorldSage, a for-profit higher education system to address education for the 21st Century and Interschola, a company that helps education clients turn idle assets into cash by selling the goods via online auctions, as well as several education technology companies, including Fablevision. Among numerous honors, Dr. Kurshan received the Education Academic Society's Making It Happen Award and the Highest Leaf Award from the Women's Venture Fund.  She is listed in Who's Who in Technology Today. 
leadership.bobbi.part4=Dr. Kurshan received her Ed.D. and M.S. from Virginia Tech University and her B.S. from Newcomb College ? Tulane University.

leadership.anne.qualifiedName=Anne Schreiber, Chief Academic Officer

leadership.anne.part1=Anne Schreiber is a seasoned multi-media publisher, product designer and educator.  She joins Curriki as its Chief Academic Officer where she will oversee the creation and quality of the curricula on curriki.org.
leadership.anne.part2=Before joining Curriki, Anne was Vice President of Product at the Grow Network/McGraw-Hill, an assessment and instructional reporting company, providing customized instruction based on summative assessment data. Prior to that she was the Publisher of secondary products at Scholastic where she published 'Scholastic Reading Counts' and 'The Scholastic Reading Inventory'.  She created and directed the development of science content for two award-winning science products: 'The Magic School Bus' television series and 'Scholastic Science Place'.  She also directed the creation of Scholastic's highly successful, award-winning beginning literacy system, 'WiggleWorks'.
leadership.anne.part3=Earlier in her career, Anne held numerous programming and curriculum development positions including Vice President of Content and Programming at bigchalk and Managing Editor of Time Warner's parenting Web site, ParentTime. While at Sesame Street Workshop, Anne developed curriculum for the school and community markets utilizing the assets of CTW's flagship science show, '3-2-1 CONTACT'.  Anne began her career as an elementary school teacher, developing staff and student enrichment programs. 
leadership.anne.part4=Anne did both her undergraduate and graduate work in Curriculum and Instruction and Science Education at Cornell University. She is the author of more than a dozen books for young children.

leadership.joshua.qualifiedName=Joshua Marks, Chief Technology Officer

leadership.joshua.part1=Joshua Marks has focused his 20-year-long career on using emerging technologies to enable and improve learning opportunities for all children in both formal and informal settings. As Chief Technology Officer, Joshua oversees all technology development and hosting infrastructure for Curriki.org. In this role Joshua sets the technical direction, manages the development teams and collaborates with partners, contributors and the open source software community to design and provide the tools needed to realize Curriki's innovative vision. Joshua is also the point person for engaging with standards groups such as IMS Global and SIF (The schools Interoperability Framework).  
leadership.joshua.part2=Before joining Curriki, Joshua was a Senior Systems Architect at CTB/McGraw-Hill where he was responsible for enterprise technology renewal and completed a total re-design of the company's online assessment system to enable back-end integration with legacy 'paper and pencil' scoring and reporting systems. Prior to that, he was Senior Director eLearning Technology at Harcourt Education where he was instrumental in launching Harcourt Education?s e-learning group to foster technological innovation within and across the traditionally print-based Harcourt publishing companies. He also spearheaded a first-of-its-kind tablet PC 1-to-1 e-learning pilot project with 150 middle school students in partnership with Microsoft and HP as vision for the future of educational publishing.
leadership.joshua.part3=Earlier in his career, Joshua was co-founder and CTO for the ZapMe! Knowledge Network, a broadband satellite delivered network for K-12 education. Before the advent of the internet, Joshua pioneered the use of personal computers in learning as a Producer of award winning early learning games at Electronic Arts and as the 20th employee of The Learning Company with credits that include the original Reader Rabbit, The Children's Writing &amp; Publishing Center, The Bilingual Writing Center, Challenge of the Ancient Empires, the School House Rock series, The Story Painting series, Scooter's Magic Castle, among many others. Joshua started his career as a Software Librarian for the Mendocino County Superintendent of School in Northern California where he grew up. Joshua holds a degree in Mathematics from University of California at Santa Cruz (UCSC) where he now lives.



#Main.LearnMore

learnmore.title=More About Curriki

learnmore.intro=Curriki is where all of us -- our community of educators, parents and students can work together to develop interesting, creative and effective educational materials that the global educational community can use for free. 

learnmore.ourGoal=Our goal is to:
learnmore.ourGoal.1=Develop curriculum through community contributors
learnmore.ourGoal.2=Deliver the curriculum globally
learnmore.ourGoal.3=Determine the impact by project and by individual

learnmore.initialFocus=The initial focus is on K-12 curricula in the areas of mathematics, science, technology, reading and language arts, and languages.

learnmore.currikiWhitePaper=Click [here&gt;{0}] to read a white paper about how Curriki will help make quality open source curricula freely available to all. 

learnmore.educationalSupportAndPublishingTools.subtitle=Educational Support and Publishing Tools

learnmore.educationalSupportAndPublishingTools.part1=Our online setup will make it easy to post a wide variety of different resources, courses and curricula.  We will encourage community members to review, edit, revise and combine resources into courses and complete curricula. To help you do this, we are providing a comprehensive curricular framework that includes defined learning objectives, scope and sequence for instruction, lesson plans, student activities, instructional materials, and  teacher training.  Assessments will enable students and parents to monitor progress and performance. 
learnmore.educationalSupportAndPublishingTools.part2=Once we are fully up and running, curriculum developers will be able to get the community's feedback and evaluation of their work. Subject matter experts will review and comment on the curricula with local education administration support, which will also ensure that the content meets accreditation standards for the relevant regions.
learnmore.educationalSupportAndPublishingTools.part3=Curriki's publishing tools will simplify the process of creating content and providing information about your resources so that others can locate them easily.  This will make it easy to systematically describe your materials, include assessments, and align them to curriculum frameworks or standards. 
learnmore.educationalSupportAndPublishingTools.part4=In the future, It is our intention that Curriki curricula will be translated and adapted so it can be used as the basis for creating localized versions.

learnmore.aboutTechno.subtitle=About the Technology

learnmore.aboutTechno.part1=Curriki is based on an open source technology, a Wiki, which makes it easy to post materials online.  When community members view the resource pages, they are able to comment, edit, and group together content to create a lesson, course or curriculum.
learnmore.aboutTechno.part2=Other technologies will be available In the future, such as bulletin boards, blogs and podcasts to enable collaboration between contributors and users of the content to improve the curricula.

learnmore.groups.subtitle=Groups

learnmore.groups.part1=Every community has groups of folks with similar interests or goals, and Curriki is no exception. Curriki groups provide a way for educators to get together and exchange ideas, discuss issues and targeted resources, or just to talk about what has worked (or not) in your efforts to educate and In your desire to spread the word 
learnmore.groups.part2=As we develop, special groups will be formed to work on specific Issues and solve related problems. 

learnmore.moreInfo.subtitle=More Information



#Main.McNealy

mcnealy.title=Board of Directors

mcnealy.fullName=Scott G. McNealy
mcnealy.role=Member, Board of Directors

mcnealy.part1=As a member of Curriki's Board of Directors and the visionary behind the idea for Curriki, Scott G. McNealy will help guide the organization's goal of making world-class curricula universally accessible.  
mcnealy.part2=Currently Chairman of Sun Microsystems, Inc.'s Board of Directors, McNealy co-founded the company in 1982. He served as chief executive officer and chairman at Sun for 22 years, steering the Company to constant innovation in open, network computing. He also helped transform the company from a Silicon Valley start-up to a leading provider of network computing infrastructure with more than 30,000 employees worldwide, all while positioning the Company as the model of corporate integrity.
mcnealy.part3=McNealy is known for his longstanding commitment to education and advocacy for open and competitive business practices. In March 2004, he led Sun to create the Global Education &amp; Learning Community (GELC) to leverage open source to provide affordable lifelong learning for all students, no matter where they are. GELC was spun off in 2006 as an independent 501(c)(3) nonprofit now known as Curriki - the Global Education &amp; Learning Community.  
mcnealy.part4=McNealy holds a Bachelors of Arts from Harvard with a Bachelors of Arts in Economics and received a Masters of Business Administration from Stanford University. 



#Main.nroccourses

nroccourses.requirements=Hardware and Software Requirements
nroccourses.requirements.user=User Requirements

nroccourses.envScience=Environmental Science

nroccourses.calculus=Calculus
nroccourses.calculus.intro1=Introductory Calculus 1
nroccourses.calculus.intro2=Introductory Calculus 2
nroccourses.calculus.general1=General Calculus 1
nroccourses.calculus.general2=General Calculus 2


nroccourses.physics=Physics
nroccourses.physics.intro1=Introductory Physics 1
nroccourses.physics.intro2=Introductory Physics 2
nroccourses.physics.general1=General Physics 1
nroccourses.physics.general2=General Physics 2



#Main.OpenSource

opensource.currikiDef=Curriki Open Source Definition

opensource.currikiExplanation=Curriki Open Source Explanation
opensource.licenceExplanation=Simple Curriki License Explanation



#Main.Partners

partners.title=Partners and Sponsors

partners.intro=Curriki is a community of partners who are all working to improve education by using technology to make learning resources readily available to all who need them.  Our work is facilitated by our partners who have generously shared their resources with us, as well as sponsors who have supported our efforts with funding or technology. Click the links below to learn more about these supporters.

partners.interestedToBeSponsor=Interested in becoming a sponsor?

partners.publisherPartner=If you're a publisher or other organization with a substantial collection of K-12 curriculum, share it with the global education community. Email us and tell us about your content:

partners.congruent.name=Congruent Solutions, Inc.
partners.congruent.intro=Congruent, the single source for business technology needs, has supported Curriki by providing engineering, QA and content conversion services to the project team.
partners.congruent.visit=Visit Congruent

partners.innovation.name=DfES Next Practices Initiative
partners.innovation.intro=The British Department for Education and Skills supports a strategic approach to the future development of communication technologies in education, and children's services as a means to transforming teaching, learning and helping to improve outcomes for children and young people. The Next Practices initiative helps accomplish this through shared ideas, more exciting lessons and online help for professionals.
partners.innovation.visit=Visit DFES

partners.elluminate.name=Elluminate
partners.elluminate.intro=Elluminate is a leading provider of live Web conferencing and eLearning solutions for corporate and academic meetings. Elluminate ensures the best user experience through superior quality voice over Internet regardless of connection speed or  operating system.   The software provides advanced yet easy-to-use moderator tools that help create a rich, collaborative environment for live online interaction.
partners.elluminate.visit=Visit Elluminate
partners.elluminate.startConf=Start a conference using Elluminate

partners.fortis.name=Fortis General Counsel, LLP
partners.fortis.intro=Robert Dang, of Fortis General Counsel, LLP, has generously provided  Curriki with legal counsel.  Fortis General Counsel, LLP is a boutique law firm that provides general counsel services, as well as traditional corporate and technology licensing legal services, to emerging growth companies primarily in the technology sector.
partners.fortis.visit=Visit Fortis General Counsel

partners.fhsst.name=Free High School Science Texts
partners.fhsst.intro=FHSST aims to provide free science and mathematics textbooks for Grades 10 - 12 learners by encouraging educators and scientists from all over the world to contribute and edit content that will, ultimately, become textbooks.  These books will be available for free, over the Internet, for use by teachers and students who need them. 
partners.fhsst.seeMore=See more about FHSST
partners.fhsst.sample=View sample chapter

partners.jes.name=Jes &amp; Co.
partners.jes.intro=JES &amp; Co. is committed to providing youth with balanced environments that enable development of effective communication skills through the use of technology. 
partners.jes.visit=Visit JES &amp; Co.

partners.keris.name=Korea Education &amp; Research Information
partners.keris.intro=KERIS is dedicated to creating improvement in the quality of public education and development of human resources through e-Learning support systems. KERIS is partnering with Curriki on the integration of their GMAT (Global Metadata Automatic Translation) solution for improving the quality of search results for the global repository.
partners.keris.visit=Visit Keris

partners.nroc.name=NROC
partners.nroc.intro=The National Repository of Online Courses network is sponsored by the Monterrey Institute for Technology and Education (MITE). As part of MITE's ongoing efforts to improve access to education, NROC is an online community of educators, designers, technologists, and administrators working together to develop high-quality online education that is available to everyone. 
partners.nroc.visit=Learn more about NROC
partners.nroc.sample=View Sample NROC Courses

partners.sun.name=Sun Microsystems
partners.sun.intro=Sun supports the notion that an Open Source curriculum repository is a key element in improving the quality and reach of education throughout the world.  Sun began to act on this vision when, in 2004, it founded the Global Education Learning Community, Curriki?s predecessor, was founded by Sun.
partners.sun.visit=Visit Sun's Open Source in Education site

partners.millennium.name=UN Millennium Project Digital Storytelling Effort
partners.millennium.intro=Tapestry, a digital storytelling initiative conceived under the United Nations Millennium Campaign. Tapestry is designed to give young leaders a way of describing their activities in support of the Millennium Development Goals.
partners.millennium.learnMoreTapestry=Learn More about the Tapestry Project
partners.millennium.digitalStories=View digital stories

partners.unSport.name=The United Nations Sport for Development and Peace
partners.unSport.intro=For many years the United Nations, its funds, programs and related specialized agencies have acknowledged the importance of sports in society. The UN is bringing the power of sports to help in the global fight against disease, social exclusion and environmental degradation. 
partners.unSport.visit=Visit UN Sport for Development and Peace

partners.wlc.name=The World Leadership Corps
partners.wlc.intro=WLC advocates the creation of an international service program that unites the energy and idealism of youth with the power of digital media to prepare tomorrow's leaders to meet global educational needs and to build awareness of critical issues facing the planet in this new century.  WLC currently has volunteers in Sweden and China who are working with Curriki to create and utilize open source learning resources.
partners.wlc.visit=Learn more about the WLC

partners.xwiki.name=XWiki
partners.xwiki.intro=XWiki is the Open Source wiki software on which Curriki is built. Chosen for its strength and flexibility, XWiki offers a high-quality solution for Curriki's design challenges, which require a mix of free-to-edit and structured contents. Created in 2004, XWiki.com aims to provide collaborative work interfaces based on its Open-Source software.
partners.xwiki.visit=Visit XWiki


#Main.PrivacyPolicy

privacyPolicy.title=Curriki Privacy Policy
privacyPolicy.downloadAsPDF=Download a PDF of the Curriki Privacy Policy

privacyPolicy.infoAndUse.title=Information Collection &amp; Use

privacyPolicy.registration.subtitle=Registration
privacyPolicy.registration.part1=In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give contact information (such as your email address). 
privacyPolicy.registration.part2=Curriki is the sole owner of the contact and usage information collected on Curriki.org. Curriki collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

privacyPolicy.log.subtitle=Log Files
privacyPolicy.log.part1=As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  
privacyPolicy.log.part2=We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  
privacyPolicy.log.part3=We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.  However, your account is associated with any and all contributions you make to the site and you are responsible for adhering to all presently published IP policies. 

privacyPolicy.cookies.subtitle=Cookies
privacyPolicy.cookies.part1=A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's 'help' file. 
privacyPolicy.cookies.part2=We set a persistent cookie to store your User Name and Passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  
privacyPolicy.cookies.part3=If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, may be limited. 
privacyPolicy.cookies.part4=This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Curriki only.

privacyPolicy.profile.subtitle=Profile
privacyPolicy.profile.part1=We store information that we collect through registration and the contributions you make to the community to create a 'profile' of your preferences and activities, to serve the community and to enforce IP and use policies. All contributions you make on the site are linked to your user profile and login/screen name. If you have shared your profile, any member of the site can view your profile and the information stored there (except your password) and all of your published contributions (but not your unpublished contributions). Even if you choose to keep your profile private, all members can see your published contributions and that your screen name is associated with the contribution.  
privacyPolicy.profile.part2=We do not share your profile with other third parties.

privacyPolicy.infoUse.subtitle=Uses of Information
privacyPolicy.infoUse=Curriki collects personal information that you disclose when you register with the site and through your use of the services on the site. Curriki automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Curriki cookies, the contributions you make and the page you request.  Curriki uses information for the following general purposes, to: monitor traffic, improve our services, enforce terms of use and IP policies, contact you, and conduct research.

privacyPolicy.commsFromCurriki.title=Communications from the Site

privacyPolicy.news.subtitle=Newsletters and Site Pages
privacyPolicy.news=If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) or 'Watch' pages on our site, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter or page to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the 'Choice and Opt-out' section.

privacyPolicy.serviceAnnouncements.subtitle=Service-Related Announcements
privacyPolicy.serviceAnnouncements.part1=We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.  
privacyPolicy.serviceAnnouncements.part2=Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

privacyPolicy.customer.subtitle=Customer Service
privacyPolicy.customer=Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request as reasonable.

privacyPolicy.sharingInfo.title=Information Sharing and Disclosure

privacyPolicy.personallyInfo.subtitle=Personally Identifiable Information
privacyPolicy.personallyInfo.part1=We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties as long as you keep your user profile private. Curriki does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you collected in connection with your use of the Curriki Website with other people or entities, except as otherwise specified.
privacyPolicy.personallyInfo.part2=If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your profile by making the change on our member information page ('My Curriki') or by sending an e-mail to webmaster@curriki.org or by contacting though any method described in the Curriki Contact Page.

privacyPolicy.externalLinks.subtitle=Links to Other Sites
privacyPolicy.externalLinks.part1=This Web site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Curriki. Please be aware that we, Curriki, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
privacyPolicy.externalLinks.part2=We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  
privacyPolicy.externalLinks.part3=This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

privacyPolicy.cobrandedSites.subtitle=Co-Branded Sites
privacyPolicy.cobrandedSites=Curriki works with partners to provide services to the community. One such partnership is with Elluminate who provides a hosted service application for group collaboration, application sharing, conferencing and white boarding. Curriki does not share your information with Elluminate, however, when using their application you may be asked to provide a screen name (Or Curriki may provide your Curriki screen name), and all your activities and information provided are governed by Elluminate's agreements and policies. Please be sure to review Elluminate's policies before using the service linked on the Curriki site.  

privacyPolicy.boardsAndChats.subtitle=Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms
privacyPolicy.boardsAndChats=Curriki is a service dedicated to supporting learning communities. Curriki provides many on-line tools for users to contribute and participate in the community; in addition to comments and message boards, Curriki provides users the ability to contribute and share content, and to work collaboratively on content development projects. If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, or use any of the other contributory and participatory functions, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums, share in your profile, and share in the resources you contribute or otherwise disclose on the site. 

privacyPolicy.security.subtitle=Security
privacyPolicy.security.part1=We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
privacyPolicy.security.part2=If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at 

privacyPolicy.businessTransitions.subtitle=Business Transitions
privacyPolicy.businessTransitions=In the event Curriki goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another entity, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

privacyPolicy.disclamer.title=Legal Disclaimer
privacyPolicy.disclamer=We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Curriki.

privacyPolicy.optOut.title=Choice or Opt-Out
privacyPolicy.optOut=We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your profile visible to visitors and other members. You can indicate your preference in your account settings.  You can also choose which pages you would like to watch and what mailings to receive. You can also delete your account or send a request, using the e-mail address listed in the account, to {0} to have your account removed from the system. 

privacyPolicy.changes.title=Changes in This Privacy Statement
privacyPolicy.changes=We reserve the right to amend or modify our privacy policy at any time.  If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

privacyPolicy.contact.title=Contact Us
privacyPolicy.contact=If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at {0} or mail or call us at:


#Main.Search

search.overload=Search is not available at this point due to the success of the Curriki Web site overloading our servers.


#Main.SearchResources

searchResources.rebuilding=Started index rebuild with {0} documents. Will take some time depending on the number of pages/attachments.
searchResources.rebuildFailed=Index rebuild failed.

searchResources.searchTable.course=Course
searchResources.searchTable.publishedDate=Published Date
searchResources.searchTable.contributor=Contributor
searchResources.searchTable.actions=Actions

searchResources.noResult=You search did not return matching resources.
searchResources.error=Error loading search



#Main.sitemap

sitemap.title=Provisional Site Map

</content></xwikidoc>