<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xwikidoc>
<web>XWiki</web>
<name>XMLapplications</name>
<language></language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>0</translation>
<parent>XWiki.Stories</parent>
<creator>XWiki.gtext</creator>
<author>XWiki.gtext</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.gtext</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1154194415000</creationDate>
<date>1154194777000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1266877070000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.1</version>
<title></title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<comment>Importé depuis un le XAR</comment>
<minorEdit>false</minorEdit>
<syntaxId>xwiki/1.0</syntaxId>
<hidden>false</hidden>
<content>&lt;blockquote style="border: 1px solid black; padding: 1em; background: linen none repeat scroll 0% 50%; -moz-background-clip: -moz-initial; -moz-background-origin: -moz-initial; -moz-background-inline-policy: -moz-initial;"&gt;

*Applications of XML*


Before we start learning more about how an XML document is structured, let&amp;acute;s point for what XML can be used for. The four major applications of XML deal with:


*Publication*: Database content can be converted into XML and afterwards into HTML by using an XSLT stylesheet. By this way complex websites as well as print media like pdf files can be created. XML is an ideal intermediary format between XSLT and HTML. Information no longer has to be inserted into different medias (RTF/DOC, PDF, WWW) from different sources. With XML it can be first converted in the neutral XML format. From this, with the appropriate layout sheets and transformations, brochures, websites or datalists can be generated.


An example for the capability of XML and XSLT gives the website [EMI Music&gt;http://www.emimusic.de]. The website contains approximately 20.000 single sites with profiles of the artists, their products and the titles of the songs. These sites are generated with a XSLT script. On basis of the used script the production of a catalog in pdf format is also possible. Please see below for more details.


*Interaction*: XML can be used for accesing and changing data interactively. This man-machine communication usually happens via browser.


*Integration* By using XML homogenous and heterogenous applications can be integrated. XML is used to describe data, interfaces and protocols. This machine-machine communication helps integrating relational databases (e.g. by importing/exporting different formats)


*Transaction*: XML helps processing transactions of applications like online marketplaces, supply chain management and e-procurement systems.

&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content></xwikidoc>
